let savollar10 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "benefit",
        answer: "A. foyda",
        options: [
            "A. foyda",
            "B. zarar",
            "C. muammo",
            "D. to'siq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "certain",
        answer: "B. ishonchi komil",
        options: [
            "A. ikkilangan",
            "B. ishonchi komil",
            "C. shubhali",
            "D. noma'lum"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "chance",
        answer: "A. imkoniyat",
        options: [
            "A. imkoniyat",
            "B. xavf",
            "C. yo'qotish",
            "D. zarar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "effect",
        answer: "C. ta'sir",
        options: [
            "A. sabab",
            "B. asos",
            "C. ta'sir",
            "D. natija"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "essential",
        answer: "D. muhim",
        options: [
            "A. ahamiyatsiz",
            "B. ikkilamchi",
            "C. befarq",
            "D. muhim"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "far",
        answer: "B. uzoq",
        options: [
            "A. yaqin",
            "B. uzoq",
            "C. tor",
            "D. qisqa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to focus",
        answer: "A. diqqatni qaratmoq",
        options: [
            "A. diqqatni qaratmoq",
            "B. hayol qilmoq",
            "C. chalg'imoq",
            "D. anglamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "function",
        answer: "D. vazifa",
        options: [
            "A. xato",
            "B. zarar",
            "C. muammo",
            "D. vazifa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "grass",
        answer: "C. o't",
        options: [
            "A. daraxt",
            "B. buta",
            "C. o't",
            "D. gul"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "to guard",
        answer: "B. qo'riqlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "B. qo'riqlamoq",
            "C. xavfga solmoq",
            "D. beparvo bo'lmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "image",
        answer: "A. rasm",
        options: [
            "A. rasm",
            "B. ovoz",
            "C. hid",
            "D. tuyg'u"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "immediate",
        answer: "C. tezkor",
        options: [
            "A. kechikkan",
            "B. keyinroq",
            "C. tezkor",
            "D. sekin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "primary",
        answer: "D. asosiy",
        options: [
            "A. ikkinchi darajali",
            "B. ahamiyatsiz",
            "C. ikkilamchi",
            "D. asosiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "proud",
        answer: "B. faxrlangan",
        options: [
            "A. uyatli",
            "B. faxrlangan",
            "C. xafa",
            "D. qayg'uli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to remain",
        answer: "A. qolmoq",
        options: [
            "A. qolmoq",
            "B. ketmoq",
            "C. yo'qolmoq",
            "D. chetga chiqmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "to rest",
        answer: "C. dam olmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ishlamoq",
            "B. yugurmoq",
            "C. dam olmoq",
            "D. chopmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "separate",
        answer: "D. alohida",
        options: [
            "A. birlashgan",
            "B. birga",
            "C. birlashgan",
            "D. alohida"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "site",
        answer: "A. joy",
        options: [
            "A. joy",
            "B. vaqt",
            "C. shaxs",
            "D. obyekt"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "tail",
        answer: "B. dum",
        options: [
            "A. bosh",
            "B. dum",
            "C. panja",
            "D. quloq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "trouble",
        answer: "C. muammo",
        options: [
            "A. yechim",
            "B. quvonch",
            "C. muammo",
            "D. muvaffaqiyat"
        ]
    }
];
